hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is Jared
microkowski and on this podcast I share
with you strategies and tips that can
help you grow your mentorship business
your coaching business if you're an
author speaker trainer how to get more
clients actually pay you money not just
be by sharing information with people
but actually getting people to pay you
for the knowledge that you have and
that's what my passion is is seeing
mentors and coaches become extremely
wealthy online I have two decades of
experience in this industry and we've
built multiple eight-figure mentorship
businesses during that time and I want
to pass on to you what's working right
now to help you break past to the next
level and something I want to talk about
is Letting Go
about everybody else thinks about you
letting go of the opinions
of prospects and even clients is going
to help you become a better Coach
because if we're so focused on managing
and maintaining other people's feelings
or emotions
we're not going to be operating at our
best because we're too focused on how we
look to others rather than what's going
to actually get them results and that's
what I have noticed over the years you
know I I didn't want people to be upset
with me I wanted my message to resonate
with people but I was tiptoeing around
the real issues that people needed
sometimes people they just need the hard
truth and they need the consequences of
their choices and actions laid out in
front of them so they can see that and
that's painful to see people as you're
mentoring them are going to have up and
down days they're going to have losses
and they're going to have wins and both
times you need to be able to mentor and
raise people up in that level
when you go out there to build a
coaching and mentorship business
you do all the right things and still
have haters
on social media people who don't like
your message don't like what you're
saying disagree with you are there just
to conflict with you and even discredit
you and they they get off on this
they're they they actually find a sense
of self-worth in doing this with people
by criticizing and pointing out where
everybody's wrong in their life and I've
been to the point in my business to not
engage with those people and not to do
business with those people and and and
it used to give me really caught up
because
I was finding that I was a magnet for
these type of people like
multiple per week wanting to get into
arguments and debates why my methods
don't actually work and why you know
those things that I'm teaching are
actually not helping people and I was
just like shocked by the fact that
people wanted to spend time to discuss
how wrong they felt that I was and what
I was saying in my methodologies I mean
even even a training like this right
here
uh would be an example of that and I
would get I would get DMS and messages
people wanted to debate this I would and
and the problem was is that I was
spending my time around people who just
wanted to debate things they just they
they found their senses of self-worth in
being right
proving others wrong and proving their
opinions right and and and and
the unfortunate part is for me I think
because of unhealed trauma that I was
working through is I would freeze up in
these types of situations I would
struggle to even communicate with people
and I would struggle to
um do the best thing in my business
because I was so concerned as to what
other people would think I'm still
growing in this area this is still an
area that I'm growing in actively I can
tell you every single time when I have
completely let go of
other people's opinions concerning
myself do they accept me do they agree
with me are they going to like what I'm
gonna say are they gonna resonate with
it and I go out there
in my business and just make it a point
to help people get really rich and to
make a ton of money and to get results
and walk people through the process that
we've done and are doing to do that see
that's
that's what gets people results that's
what produces what people are actually
willing to pay me money for me trying to
make sure that Elizabeth's feelings are
heard and you know not saying something
too harshly because I'm afraid of coming
across
in a way that might not resonate like
that Separates Me from actually being
able to be effective to help people as a
coach and mentor
that's what I found it says that I'm
actually giving people a lower quality
version of myself so they're not
actually getting all of what they paid
for uh By Me by me doing that and in a
sense I'm actually
um
this is like a decision that I've made
is that for me to operate in excellence
and actually deliver
on the promises that I've made to people
I can't tiptoe around people's emotions
and feelings and I will upset people and
I will disappoint them and they might
not always be happy with what I have to
say
they may
take it to an extreme level even
in how upset they get and yet I can't
let that change what I choose to do in
my business now oh gosh empathy is an
incredible thing in business
being able to empathize with people in
their situation
that's it's an incredible thing for
marketing being able to empathize what
motivates people this isn't what I'm
talking about with empathy I'm talking
about when you're being criticized
judged put down and discredited and
people are trying to get you to second
guess in question
what you know to be true
uh that's not empathy
that's called negativity and I don't
tolerate that I I focus on positivity
and joy in our atmosphere and and and
creating an Abundant Life full of riches
full of wealth not just a little bit of
money a lot of money
I have people who follow me they're not
happy with the fact that I talk so much
about making a ton of money
in your business and yet that's that's
my focus is helping people make a ton of
money in a business as a mentor and as a
coach I believe that the most important
thing that you can do as a mentor and
Coach is to increase your cash flow to
make as much money as possible
we're way too concerned with what other
people think about us are they going to
accept us are they going to quit
early
and you know I see people they justify
it's like well I'm just beginning well
I'm just starting I really think that
you have to have the mindset of a
multi-millionaire
to get to the next level that you want
to get to
instead of waiting until you reach that
level to then shift your mindset
it takes Shifting the mindset first
to then start to see the changes in the
results in your life and it takes taking
risks and stepping out
not asking for permission not trying to
make sure that everybody is pleased or
appeased with you
and when you can do this as a mentor and
as a coach and you combine this with
empathy and you combine this with being
able to see what do people need help
with how can we solve problems for them
how can we lead people to the goals that
they have you'll have a highly
successful highly profitable business
by doing this now authenticity alone is
not enough you need to then market and
promote your business and you need to
actually find people actively through
marketing and advertising campaigns that
are looking for what you have to offer
and then once you find them
using your best sales skills and sales
ability you end up closing those people
as paid clients for you
anything that comes in the way of you
closing sales in your business
with qualified prospects
which is like one one of the
simplest and easiest things in the world
to do but
a lot of people because of what's in
between their two ears struggle with it
because they're so focused on being
worried about something that's probably
never going to happen
of what people might think about them
and trying to avoid people perceiving
them or thinking something about them
that they don't want or trying to
control what people are doing the desire
to even make people become your client
itself
being so rooted in controlling other
people
when I go out there I could not care
less if somebody becomes a client or not
at all
and that's the right energy that is
actually attractive that actually brings
clients to us is when we're not
so focused on I need to make this happen
and we operate out of desperation which
is
repulsive
to people smells like stinky trash
smells like stinky garbage
to people
when you're so desperate and need them
to quote unquote do something or become
a client of yours and people will sense
it and people will read it and people
will smell it
a mile away because it just it reeks
and nobody wants to be around a coach or
Mentor that does that and yet that is
what 99 of coaches and mentors when they
go out there to Market their business
are doing they're reeking of desperation
instead of simply just connecting with
potential clients giving their best
content away giving value actually
solving problems for people not just
teasing the problem
that's one part of it and then boldly
and confidently selling something that's
irresistible that the person that
they're selling to literally feels like
and believes that they they can't live
without it
and so you can simultaneously do those
two things you attract the right people
by solving a problem immediately for
them not a bait and switch not a teaser
but an actual problem
and then you build trust with people to
where they believe that they can't live
without joining your coaching program
that's the win-win basis
of effectively building a coaching
business and that's not hard to do uh
it's not sleazy it's not slimy it's not
even it's not manipulative in any way
it's about
how you frame
the conversation
the value you deliver
and how you actually connect
with your target prospect it's possible
for you to make twenty to forty thousand
dollars a month starting with a
mentorship business but most people
barely scratch the surface of even a
thousand dollars a month because they're
so concerned with doing everything right
quote unquote According to some
arbitrary version of right that somebody
made up at some point in time
and that now we are taking in as I have
to do things this way in order to
succeed
when really
making your this your one Focus your one
Focus
how do I find people that are
potentially able to become clients of my
mentoring and coaching business if
you're just starting out you don't know
your Niche or you don't know what you
coach on start there
figure that out and then find as many
people that can validate that you picked
the right topic or niche if nobody has
an interest in it if nobody's buying
from you if nobody's showing up
pivot or adjust it One Direction or
another
a little bit closer to what people are
actually wanting one of the best ways to
learn what people actually want is the
feedback loop getting feedback from
people what they want what they desire
in their own words where they tell you
in my business I have a 100 page
document of all of the struggles and
frustrations and desires the people who
join my free webinars have told me that
they want and I use this as a reference
of how to talk and how to communicate to
get more clients in their businesses and
how to present all of my offers and
webinars that are online all of my
content is geared around
helping these people get results
helping you get results if you're
listening to this right now if you're
watching this
I want to help you as a mentor and Coach
start your business
launch it get a ton of clients with
Facebook ads and make a ton of money
that's what we help you with that's what
we walk you through and that's what we
follow the process of okay and so if
you're a part of our community
don't just listen to the content be
active go ask me questions on my social
media
go ask me questions on my YouTube
channel join us in one of our Live
Events and if you're not part of our
client growth accelerator program jump
into the client growth accelerator
program the next time that we open the
doors to it it's the best program that's
out there with exclusive training as
well as access to me the only way you
can access me is through this program
it's the way to get exclusive access to
me to work with you on your business and
to help you grow okay and so I'd love to
help you I'd love to work with you
I'd love to help you get multiple six
and seven figure results in your
business
stay plugged into the podcast
and we'll see in the accelerator we'll
talk soon
[Music]
[Applause]